streamingvideoprovider.co.uk 2011-06-21

# Privacy Policy

StreamingVideoProvider Ltd  ("StreamingVideoProvider") values the privacy of our users, members, and others who use [www.StreamingVideoProvider.com](http://www.streamingvideoprovider.com/)  , [www.StreamingVideoProvider.co.uk](http://www.streamingvideoprovider.co.uk/) and any other web sites or services owned or operated by StreamingVideoProvider (the "StreamingVideoProvider Sites") (collectively or individually, "Users").

This Privacy Notice is incorporated into and is subject to the StreamingVideoProvider [Terms of Use](http://www.streamingvideoprovider.co.uk/index.php?a=article&it=terms). Your use of the StreamingVideoProvider Sites and any personal information you provide on the StreamingVideoProvider Sites remains subject to the terms of this Privacy Notice and our [Terms of Use](http://www.streamingvideoprovider.co.uk/index.php?a=article&it=terms).  

Please note that any video, image, blog entry, or other content posted at the direction of Users onto the StreamingVideoProvider Sites becomes publicly-available content, is not considered personally identifiable information subject to this Privacy Notice, and may be collected and used by others.  

NOTE TO KIDS: THE STREAMINGVIDEOPROVIDER SITES ARE NOT FOR PERSONS UNDER THE AGE OF 13. If you are under 13 years of age, please visit another site - there are lots of other great web sites for you.

**_The Information StreamingVideoProvider Collects:_**

User Provided Information: You may provide to StreamingVideoProvider what is generally called "personally identifiable" information (such as your name and email address) when you choose to participate in the various activities offered on the StreamingVideoProvider Sites such as uploading videos, posting messages and blogging, reviewing and rating videos, entering surveys and contests, and subscribing to newsletters.  
"Cookies" Information: When you visit the StreamingVideoProvider Sites, we may send one or more cookies - a small text file containing a string of alphanumeric characters - to your computer. StreamingVideoProvider uses both session cookies and persistent cookies. A session cookie disappears after you close your browser. A persistent cookie remains after you close your browser and may be used by your browser on subsequent visits to the StreamingVideoProvider Sites. Persistent cookies can be removed, but each web browser is a little different, so please look through your browser "Help" file to learn the correct way to modify your cookies set-up.  
"Automatically Collected" Information: When you visit the StreamingVideoProvider Sites or open one of our HTML emails, we may automatically record certain information from your web browser by using different types of technology, including "clear gifs" or "web beacons". This "automatically collected" information may include your Internet Protocol address ("IP Address"), web browser type, the web pages or sites that you visit just before or just after the StreamingVideoProvider Sites, the pages you view on our site, and the dates and times that you visit the StreamingVideoProvider Sites.

**_

The Way StreamingVideoProvider Uses Information:

_**

1.         StreamingVideoProvider uses the information that we collect to operate, maintain, enhance, and provide to you all of the features and services found on the StreamingVideoProvider Sites. We will use your email address, without further consent, for administrative purposes such as notifying you of major StreamingVideoProvider Sites updates, for customer service, or to contact you regarding a video that you have posted.

2.         StreamingVideoProvider uses all of the information that we collect to understand the usage trends and preferences of our Users, to improve the way the StreamingVideoProvider Sites work and look, and to create new features and functionality.

3.         StreamingVideoProvider uses "automatically collected" information and "cookies" information to: (a) remember your information so that you will not have to re-enter it during your visit or the next time you visit the StreamingVideoProvider Sites; (b) provide custom, personalized advertisements, content, and information; (c) monitor the effectiveness of our marketing campaigns; (d) monitor aggregate usage metrics such as total number of visitors and pages viewed; and (e) track your entries, submissions, and status in any promotions, sweepstakes, and contests that we might host.

4.         StreamingVideoProvider will not use your email address or other personally identifiable information to send promotional or marketing messages without your consent or except as part of a specific program or feature for which you will have the ability to opt-in.

**_

When StreamingVideoProvider Discloses Information:

_**

**StreamingVideoProvider does not share your personally identifiable information with other organizations for their marketing or promotional uses without your express consent.**  
To provide web site hosting, maintenance and security, fulfill orders, offer certain functionality, improve our site, and to create new site features, we may disclose User information to affiliated companies or other businesses or persons. We require that these parties process such information in compliance with this Privacy Notice, we authorize only a limited use of such information, and we require these parties to use appropriate confidentiality measures.  
StreamingVideoProvider may share automatically collected and other aggregate non-personally-identifiable information with interested third parties to assist them in understanding the usage patterns for certain content, services, advertisements, promotions, and/or functionality on the StreamingVideoProvider Sites.  
StreamingVideoProvider may disclose User information if required to do so by law, or in the good-faith belief that such action is necessary to comply with state and federal laws (such as UK. Copyright law) or respond to a court order, judicial or other government subpoena, or warrant. We may make such disclosures without providing Users notice, in some cases.  
StreamingVideoProvider reserves the right to disclose User information that is necessary to enforce our Terms of Use; take precautions against liability; protect Users from fraudulent, abusive, or unlawful uses; to investigate and defend ourselves against third-party claims or allegations; to assist government enforcement agencies; to protect the security or integrity of the StreamingVideoProvider Sites; and to protect the rights, property, or personal safety of StreamingVideoProvider, our members, or others.

**_

Your Choices:

_**

You may, of course, decline to share personally identifiable information with StreamingVideoProvider, in which case you will not be able to upload videos or media to the StreamingVideoProvider Sites. You may update, correct, or delete your member information and email subscription preferences at any time by going to the account section of the StreamingVideoProvider Sites.   
To protect your privacy and security, we take reasonable steps to verify your identity before granting you account access or making corrections. YOU ARE RESPONSIBLE FOR MAINTAINING THE SECRECY OF YOUR UNIQUE PASSWORD AND ACCOUNT INFORMATION AT ALL TIMES.

**_

Our Commitment to Data Security:

_**

StreamingVideoProvider uses commercially reasonable physical, managerial, and technical safeguards to preserve the integrity and security of your personal information. We cannot, however, ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to StreamingVideoProvider and you do so at your own risk. Once we receive your transmission of information, StreamingVideoProvider makes commercially reasonable efforts to ensure the security of our systems. However, please note that this is not a guarantee that such information may not be accessed, disclosed, altered, or destroyed by breach of any of our physical, technical, or managerial safeguards.  
If StreamingVideoProvider learns of a security systems breach, then we may attempt to notify you electronically so that you can take appropriate protective steps. StreamingVideoProvider may post a notice on the StreamingVideoProvider Sites if a security breach occurs. Depending on where you live, you may have a legal right to receive notice of a security breach in writing. To receive a free written notice of a security breach you should notify us at [privacy@StreamingVideoProvider.com](mailto:privacy@fliqz.com).

**_

Our Commitment to Children's Privacy:

_**

Protecting the privacy of young children is especially important. For that reason, StreamingVideoProvider does not knowingly collect or maintain personally identifiable information on the StreamingVideoProvider Sites from persons under 13 years of age, and no part of our website is directed to persons under 13. IF YOU ARE UNDER 13 YEARS OF AGE, THEN PLEASE DO NOT USE OR ACCESS THE STREAMINGVIDEOPROVIDER SITES AT ANY TIME OR IN ANY MANNER. If StreamingVideoProvider learns that personally identifiable information of persons less than 13 years of age has been collected on StreamingVideoProvider without verifiable parental consent, then StreamingVideoProvider will take the appropriate steps to delete this information.

**_

Special Note to International Users:

_**

The StreamingVideoProvider Sites are hosted in the United Kingdom and are only intended for and directed to Users in the United Kingdom. If you are a User accessing the StreamingVideoProvider Sites from the European Union, United States , Asia, or any other region with laws or regulations governing personal data collection, use, and disclosure, that differ from United Kingdom laws, please be advised that through your continued use of the StreamingVideoProvider Sites, which are governed by UK. law, this Privacy Notice, and our [Terms of Use](http://www.fliqz.com/aspx/terms.aspx), you are transferring your personal information to the United Kingdom and you consent to that transfer.

**_In the Event of Merger or Sale:_**

In the event that StreamingVideoProvider is acquired by or merged with a third-party entity, we reserve the right, in any of these circumstances, to transfer or assign the information we have collected from Users as part of such merger, acquisition, sale, or other change of control.

**_

Changes and Updates to this Privacy Notice:

_**

This Privacy Notice may be revised periodically without further notice to you and this will be reflected by the "last modified" notice below. Please revisit this page to stay aware of any changes. In general, we only use your personal information in the manner described in the Privacy Notice in effect when we received that personal information. Your continued use of the StreamingVideoProvider Sites constitutes your agreement to this Privacy Notice and any future revisions.  
For revisions to this Privacy Notice that may be materially less restrictive on our use or disclosure of personal information you have provided to us, we will make reasonable efforts to notify you and obtain your consent before implementing such revisions with respect to such information.

**_Effective Date, Date Last Modified:_**

This Privacy Notice is effective as of 11 of July 2009.  

**_

StreamingVideoProvider Contact Information:

_**

Please contact StreamingVideoProvider with any questions or comments about this Privacy Notice, your personal information, our third-party disclosure practices, or your consent choices at  _[info@StreamingVideoProvider.com](mailto:info@StreamingVideoProvider.com)_. We will respond to your inquiry within 30 days of its receipt.
